<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LaTeX Quickstart on Latex Quickstart</title>
    <link>https://elu00.github.io/LatexQuickStart/</link>
    <description>Recent content in LaTeX Quickstart on Latex Quickstart</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://elu00.github.io/LatexQuickStart/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>https://elu00.github.io/LatexQuickStart/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elu00.github.io/LatexQuickStart/installation/</guid>
      <description>MiKTeX To get started with installing TeX, you&#39;ll first need to choose a variant, or &amp;quot;distribution,&amp;quot; to install. Although there previously were major difference between the different distributions, by now, most of the differences between the distributions are just historical. For this tutorial, we&#39;ll be using MiKTeX, although alternatives like TeXLive should work just as well.
 To get started then, just navigate to the MiKTeX download page and download the correct installer for your operating system (in this example, we&#39;re using Windows).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editor Setup</title>
      <link>https://elu00.github.io/LatexQuickStart/editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elu00.github.io/LatexQuickStart/editor/</guid>
      <description>Visual Studio Code While there are a plethora of different \(\LaTeX\) editors/IDEs out there, for the purposes of this class, we recommend using Visual Studio Code, a general purpose text/code editor that also comes with really nice plugin support for TeX. For the rest of this page, we&#39;ll assume you already have VS Code installed; if not, it&#39;s just another installer away at their download page.
Extension Setup After having installed MiKTeX and Perl from the last step, we&#39;ll now setup the various plugins and integrations in VS Code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Document Setup and Math Basics</title>
      <link>https://elu00.github.io/LatexQuickStart/editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elu00.github.io/LatexQuickStart/editing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Resources</title>
      <link>https://elu00.github.io/LatexQuickStart/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elu00.github.io/LatexQuickStart/resources/</guid>
      <description>Of course, this site is by no means meant to be a comprehensive tutorial on using \(\LaTeX\). If you&#39;re interested in learning more, or are looking for troubleshooting help with anything, check out the links below!
 DeTeXify - a site to help identify symbols or letters that you might not be familiar with. StackExchange - a general forum for troubleshooting or debugging. Overleaf and their documentation - an online alternative to running LaTeX locally, that also includes an excellent documentation site.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
